<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<HelpFile xmlns="http://schemas.manxads.com/HelpFile">
  <Title>Searching</Title>
  <Description>
    Learn how the ManxAds search works, how to find what you're looking
    for and get tips on creating listings which appear higher in the search results.
  </Description>
  <Body>
    <Section Title="How It Works">
      <Paragraph>
        The ManxAds Search Engine works much like Google, all the listings on
        the site are 'indexed' every so often, this is why they take a short
        while to appear after posting.
      </Paragraph>
    </Section>
    <Section Title="Advanced Searching">
      <Paragraph>
        You may want to filter your search so that it only shows listings between
        certain dates and prices, from certain categories, and even your local town or village.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        This can be done on the advanced search page (use the 'Search' link at the top of the screen).
        On this page, you can switch between advanced search, and simple search.
      </Paragraph>
    </Section>
    <Section Title="Result Ranking">
      <Paragraph>
        The ManxAds Search Engine uses a complex ranking algorithm to determine 
        how relevant a listing is in relation to the keywords you specify.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        When creating your listings, you should put the most relevant keywords
        in your title, as they carry a greater weight than those in the details.
        However, be careful you don't use a keyword too many times, or the
        search engine will see them as less unique, and so less relevant.
        Hint: Adding pictures can also improve your item's search rank.
      </Paragraph>
      <Paragraph>
        The more listings you have, the more credible your listings will be.
        When adding the listing to categories, you should try add it to as few
        as possible, your listing could loose points for being in too many.
      </Paragraph>
    </Section>
    <Section Title="Quality of Service">
      <Paragraph>
        After reading this page, if you think your listing should appear
        higher in the search results, please do contact us and tell us why
        so that we can improve the search engine.
      </Paragraph>
    </Section>
  </Body>
</HelpFile>